recently we saw 01 come out in December
there was so much fanfare about it was
because it was scoring really high or at
least the a PR mode with extra test time
compute so it was given more time to
answer questions it was doing really
well on R kgi's Benchmark the creators
on The Benchmark came out and said no
this wasn't a suitable test it never was
now we have to create something else
yeah so I feel like thinking a little
bit further ahead and creating tests
that are going to stand the test of time
you're listening to the AI native Dev
brought to you by
Tesla on today's episode of the a native
Dev we're going to have a very practical
session where we're going to be talking
with with faras here who's going to be
telling us about his perfect development
environment how he uses AI today in his
flows some of the most amazing tools
that used and hasn't used because he
hasn't had time or maybe they don't
exist so we're going to have a deep dive
into what a good AI powered developer
environment looks like and hopefully
there'll be a ton of practical tips
farath first of all tell us a little bit
about yourself so I'm a freelance
software AI engineer so I'm working on
multiple different products and I've
been using AI extensively for the last
year and a half looking into different
tools testing them out comparing them
playing around with different models and
yeah just want to use it as much in my
development workow as possible and every
time every time we chat there's always
some new tool that you mention I'm like
oh yeah now I have to add that to the
list you're you're one of the people who
is always like on the on the latest cusp
of the news and trying out new tools so
I'm really excited to have this chat
with you today we're gonna say let's
kick off with the scenario picture the
scene you're about to you sat at your
desk you're about to develop a new
application let's talk about what your
envir looks like first of all your
physical environment lights on off low
when you code during the day I'm getting
in a sunlight I'm working uh during the
night I just have a a small lamp light
up but mostly dark yeah prop proper
hacker mode okay hoodie as well what do
you what's your ideal coding drink water
just water no no caffeine no I try to
avoid it and um don't want to become
dependent I can rely on saying healthy
St fit and healthy and I keep a couple
liters
water next to me i' probably go through
them probably four times gez wow wow
snacks what your code I don't no snacks
I don't like my keyboard messy okay I
like that oh we you've got a KRON
keyboard as well right is it a clicky
one yeah it
is I once I thought now I'm working at
home this my previous Ro now I'm working
at home I can get a clicky keyboard and
not annoy anyone in the office and now I
realize how annoying it is for everyone
on Zoom as I'm tapping away I've noticed
that as well okay when you code what's
your favorite distraction do you play
music you complete silence do you have a
TV going in the background so typically
I'm in silence I enjoy just being able
to think and write down notes and that
kind of stuff but I do also still work
when I'm eating if I'm on like a lunch
break or something like that I have a
what I've started doing recently is
having the TV on yeah and I used to do
research like having my references on
one screen and uh my notes on another
now what I'm doing is with advancements
in AI tooling I've been using in for
example a cursor ID running an agentic
workflow on a easy ticket so I'm
splitting my tickets into more different
ones that I'm definitely going to have
to pay a lot of attention to but smaller
things that are that I know AI is
capable of I'll just give it to it while
I'm having a snack eating and come back
to in a few minutes if it's got done
perfect if not then just run it again so
I can even be productive when I'm yeah
yeah awesome so let's jump into that
what is your actual development
environment look like you mentioned curs
there Mac or PC PC with WSL okay and on
top of that then you mentioned cursor is
that your favorite IDE AI Dev assistant
so typically I'm using cursor nowadays I
see myself coming back to it again and
again because I just started with it and
they do release features on a regular
basis but I've got a few things a few
I'm looking at right now wind surf
recently released their wave two so they
released a bunch of features together
and they added web search and they've
already got agentic workflows where it
can do a bunch of stuff for you but now
it can do a web search where you can ask
it to implement a latest API yeah you
can go and do a web search find the top
links extract the information and then
implement it for you based on the docs
that it found and all that kind of stuff
so that is could be a game changer in
cursa I have to upload docs it does have
web search but I don't think it's as
intuitive as wi has just made it last in
the last week in the last couple days
yeah so I want to check that out there's
also kle yeah which is an open source vs
code extension MH it very much does
similar things but they recently
released a feature where you can now
select so you've already been able to
select your LMS which I love having the
choice of what large language model to
use they've added something called
architect mode and edit mode which is
stolen from another open source tool
called Ada that's C tool but architect
mode allows you to so you can select a
module to be the architect M for this
quite good options it seems like people
gravitating towards open Air's 01 and
recently deep seeks R1 M um because it's
good at thinking and it can really
create a good plan of what to great and
for the edit mode people are still
defaulting to Sonic 3.5 called son
called Sonic 3.5 it just seems to just
be sticking around even though they it
was released quite a while ago I'm
really excited to see what they're going
to release next I'm waiting on C 4 for
sure yeah interesting and you can't you
mentioned so cursa because perhaps it
was one of the first ones that you tried
and first ones you were you a vs code
user before that or yeah you were so so
so it's very familiar in terms of the ID
the UI as well and then you landed on
cursa what do you feel would be the
killer feature that would take you away
from cursor right now what's your
biggest need from the ID right now that
you don't have I'm seeing a lot so the
stuff I mentioned already are very
attractive features yeah there was a
fork of Klein recently was called rine
they just recently renamed it rodes
they've added prompt enhancement which
is pretty nice which I everyone should
do so you type in a prompt click a
button and it can improve it for you but
they also added which is even called I
think is like personalities I don't know
if that's exactly the name yeah but you
can ask it to be a QA engineer and you
can create a personality for that you
can ask it to be a uiux designer that F
that understands accessibility really
well and you can create a personality
for that so you can you can create
personalities and save them that can
behave in certain ways like certain
roles within software engineering itself
yeah that's something really cool
something I'd really like to see that I
don't haven't seen anyone do yet I've
been thinking about this for quite a
while now is style references so mid
Journey the image generator I used to
play around with it quite a lot last
year but period I was doing it every
weekend just messing around and stuff
they have this cool thing called star
reference so you can generate an image
and then provide it another image as a
starle reference it's like format
painting in your word processor you
select some text with certain formatting
select another piece of text apply that
I I think it would be really cool to
have that for code yeah so it could copy
so in mid Journey For example for the
images it copi the artistic style the
colors that kind of stuff yeah for code
it could be the language how you
structure your code the level of
commenting you do yeah all this other
kind of stuff yeah and even the
architecture or the design how you would
go about designing it so that components
that you build ex as one have a similar
architecture whether that's good or bad
yeah because every artist has their own
unit style right it's the same for
developers right we uh there is some
creativity to it there's science to it
there's some creativity to it and I'd
really like to be able to copy that MH
also when I'm looking for tools and
libraries I always find there's so many
options and this is something that's
going to help it but what would be cool
is a tool that could analyze different
libraries that do the same thing and
take the best features from each and
like that style reference I've said
before yeah do it in the certain
language that you need need it um ex
almost merge those to create something
that you is ideal for what you want your
needs yeah so this is using the fastest
um language for it this one's got this
incredible feature this one has
Integrations all these other things all
this stuff is out there so many great
devs cre even I'm seeing repos that are
huge but not the best tools and smaller
reps and even really nich things where a
sold loan developer has created a really
cool feature but it's just not gaining
attraction yeah or if you could find all
of this and then just have a tool that
merges them all together to be the
perfect yeah nice let's talk a bit
deeper into your usage of cursor I guess
do you use it for project creation from
scratch do you use it more for just like
slight changes to existing projects
what's your typical or do you do it
irrespective of what your goal is you
just go ahead and use cursor for
everything so I don't actually start
with cursor usually I go to perplexity
and do some research on what stack
libraries and tools uh would be useful
for my project so this is the tool that
I mentioned earlier that I'd like to
create would I would love to exist
because I manually go through the
different tools and libraries and look
at them analyze them see if they're
going to be good for what I'm trying to
build after the stack I'll probably then
go into cursor and build a cursor rules
file so give it some context of my
project and the rules I wanted to follow
so how it should go about writing
comments how it should make edits style
like comments that you mentioned exactly
yeah with that and then I'd probably
start coding and then as I'm I usually
tend to start with the back end so some
people like to see what they're building
first I think that is nice yeah but I
feel like the back end and the business
logic is the meat of the program and
actually for the front end I actually do
that separately so what I typically do
is go into clae and start experimenting
generating uis and it has a nice preview
in the artifacts yeah screen and then
what I do is after I've got a sitemap
with a bunch of different screens
generated I ask it to give me this in
text form I go to vzer and ask it to
generate me these pages with these
elements using a certain UI Library like
Shaden for example is one that I
typically go back to again and again
that way I get really nice consistent
pages that just have because what AI
tools don't have is taste Yeah by Prov
providing them a tool providing my UI
Library like that I can ensure a nice
quality UI and usually take the UI code
that has generated the backend stuff and
some point I merge them together asking
to group together he's quite good at
that yeah yeah when do you think about
the data model do you do that before the
backend or you go the backend and the
data model together at the same time
data model First Data model first you
data model then start building the back
end to address the data model and to
connect with the data model then the UI
on top of that exactly yeah amazing and
so everything you do in Claude is
throwaway it's prototype only and and
just trying to like almost like pulling
out a dock that that kind of describes
what you're trying to do is it a
learning thing yeah I would say it's
pretty thr away I it's more for
experimentation yeah I think AI is
really good for helping your Ida even if
you have it all in C projects or I know
chat has the same thing now as well just
opening a new chat and asking it for so
he knows it based on the documents you
provided about your project he knows
what you're trying to create he knows
maybe if you've added features that you
want he knows about those but it can
help you expand on those what features
do you think would be good for this
these user depending this a consumer
product business to business or just a
utility used by a company internally for
experimenting with ideas is really good
and even so something that I've created
is a sort of rubber ducky tool okay um
so sometimes obviously everyone as most
developers know it's quite nice to be
able to talk to someone or what of
developers do is talk to a little rubber
duck yeah uh to help them work through
problems what I've done is used open
eyes real time API to create a senior
engineer Rober duck for me so when I
think something might be the right way
to do it but I know there's other
options
I ask it okay so what are the pros and
cons of this this way of doing it do you
have any other suggestions how I could
improve this I telling it to act as a
very high level engineer yeah TI gives
me very good suggestions and I found
that I'm writing better code because of
it yeah and I think Engineers of every
level even someone at a very high level
yeah yeah having that extra advice or
that extra perspective is really useful
but especially for junior Developers for
learning when you don't know about
standards and how you should be going
about things or what technology you
should be using like when you're that
early on I remember being there you
don't know about anything that exists
you try and write everything from
scratch yeah yeah and when there are
incredible libraries and Industry
standards that you should be using yeah
convention so asking it about best
convention how to keep your code dry is
really good so let's summarize where we
are right now then you got you're about
to start a new product or new project
sorry so you dim the light slightly
great you got yourself the six gallons
of water behind you so you're drinking
some water no snacks you're hungry at
this point you start off with cursor not
cursor sorry Claude little bit of
perplexity do a bit of prototyping you
build that in get a little rule set in
cursor then you start building a cursor
data model first which you should
already know a little bit about from
your from your prototype then you start
actually building code from there in
terms of then how you then build tests
how you build documentation all those
other kind of like parts around that are
you using cursor for that is there a
second tool third tool that you use for
the other kind of like pieces there so
in terms of documentation currently I
quite like so curse is not just good at
code it's really good at text yeah right
so I'd go and start writing something in
maybe make yeah make a docs file start
writing whatever that speciic file is
about what model are you using under the
cover is it CLA again or is it
yeah which tends a lot of people tends
to say that that little bit better at
things like documentation and and and
the kind of like the written word as
well right ex so sounding like a human
right open a models maybe not so much
sometimes mhm yeah i' maybe start
writing the docs and then I can ask it
to write the rest yeah based on my
project I can pass the context on my
project ask to write the rest or if it's
writing if I'm for the data models
actually for my databases I'm typically
starting off with a general idea of what
I want asking it to expand on these and
give me suggestions and then I accept
some of the suggestions change some the
suggestions and yeah that's how I go
about it with documentation for now I
know there are better tools for theob
job I haven't started using them yet but
it's definitely on the list of something
I want to start incorporating yeah we
had the swim guys on the podcast earlier
actually which is one of which is a tool
that I see growing in popularity that
could be one to an interesting one to
look at then when you're thinking about
other things so test for example you use
CLA do you use a cursor to also write
tests and things like that or using any
of test AI test Frameworks and tools
typically right now I or do you test in
production that's cool that's a cool
answer to I start off not writing tests
I find it easier to change the code a
lot early on like early on when I'm
starting off a project I'm change the
code a lot yeah so I don't want to like
test are breaking constantly y but
afterwards I'm typically using cursor
right now okay but again I want to
experiment with a lot of other tools
yeah I know there a lot of really good
options for that yeah yeah okay cool uh
then you go to deploy any devop style
deployment tools you AI tools you use
what's your typical path to production
in my deployment at the moment I'm not
using many AI tools but I have seen some
good tools for example eraser. I which
is quite good for diagramming yeah so if
you are trying to build um a whole Cloud
architecture it can be quite good for
visualizing what you're trying to build
yeah yeah oh interesting okay cool when
we then think about I guess an
interesting one which is maybe a slight
choice or maybe not a choice these days
in terms of the language that you use to
to for your application do you care
about the language as much these days
would you dip into languages that you
are not as familiar with more likely to
because of AI tools yes I've always felt
like I'm pretty language agnostic I
started mostly python I did Java mostly
at University and I do mostly JavaScript
now but along the years I've done
probably another half dozen played
around with half dozen other languages
as well so I've already been quite
language agnostic but I'm far more
likely to dip my toes into a new
language now because I know
there's a lot less friction in being
able to learn it yeah back in the day
for example when I built a swift app
many years ago this is when Swift just
came out there were no good tutorials on
how to do anything and they were
changing the syntax every week yeah code
that I wrote one one day would be broken
the next yeah and this is happening
constantly yeah now with AI tools they
can analyze the new docs instantly as
soon as it's released they can update
the dots that they got store that
they've indexed and they can help you so
you don't need to wait on other people
other developers to create this content
for you you can go straight to the docs
the source of Truth and use that to
start expen so it's just all around a
lot easier yeah oh interesting one other
last question before we jump into come
kind of more advice based in terms of
the in terms of the flow that you've got
when you check code in PRS those types
of things any advice you'd give in and
around various PR AR tools that that
kind of like maybe do code reviews or
those types of things would do you
heavily rely on that senior developer d
as your code review I think right now I
rely on the advice I get from talking to
AI different chat and stuff like that
yeah it's something that I again want to
start implementing a code review in my
cicd so it automatically views it gives
advice and maybe even creates a a commit
with changes on a fork so I've seen a
bunch of these tools recently I heard
about sagittal ai's Neo at a event so
these are things I'm definitely looking
into starting to implement now in my
projects for sure awesome in terms of
advice like practical advice that you'd
give for developers who are trying to
build AI into their development process
uh and workflow what like the top tips
you would give a developer who is trying
to be more proficient in using AI today
in their workflows so when it comes to
building with AI I think it's really
easy to prototype but quite hard to get
into production so for those just
starting out I would start playing
around with different models yeah and
because each model feels like its own
personality imagine them like people
they respond in different ways how they
talk the limits of what they're allowed
to speak about like the guard that put
in place and compare the speed the
quality of the responses and accuracy
cost as well is a big one I'd say open
router is quite a good thing to use so
it basically has cated apis for all
these different models
and it means that you can just use put
some credit into your open router
account and start using all these
different models in your applications
yeah so that's definitely something I'd
recommend play around with both open
source and propriety models so most
people start with open AI it's
definitely open AI models definitely a
good starter but there are there's a
whole world of Open Source modelers out
there that are incredible deep seek for
example that was just released matched
open airs latest model 01 in performance
it seems from the benchmarks and a lot
of testing that people have done yeah so
play around with open source models I
feel like they're going to be very big
this year you can use if you want to
play around with them locally on your
computer you can use tools like o or LM
studio so there are a bunch of libraries
that help you build with AI for example
Lang chain is probably one that
everyone's heard of some people say it's
a little bit bloated so you can
absolutely write these things from
scratch as well and because we're at
quite an early stage it's quite it's a
really useful way to learn about how all
this stuff works with AI engineering
yeah learn how to prompt engineer this
is a really big one you can get you can
massive increase the quality of what
your sponsors you get and the products
you're building by learning how to prom
engineer properly yeah and then play
around with addons like rag which helps
you stop hallucinations uh use your own
data tools create tools and function
coing like giv get access to the web
search and other sorts of things like
this and then there are agent Frameworks
as well that you can start playing
around with to do more advanced things
they're really good to start dipping
your toes into agents and this opens up
a whole world of possibilities yeah and
then also for production you really want
to start monitoring you want monitoring
observability into the inputs and
outputs of your LM llm request you want
to monitor what's working with your
prompts and iterate on them yeah so
improve them over time to get better
responses and and also you want to run
these like thousands of times and also
we want to try and be try playing around
with adversarial prompts is your
application breaking when someone's
trying to break it like you cannot rely
on your users to always have the best of
intentions your application yeah so for
production there's so much more you need
to think about yeah yeah that's my
advice for wow so there's a whole bunch
of like things there interesting you
start with models first do you think
individuals will have two different
developers having a a preferred
different model is that based on style
is that based on accuracy and people
have different different expectations
why do you think different developers
will choose different models so
developers should try out different
models and they'll have different
profites based on their use case so you
have smaller models um which
are faster cheaper and maybe don't have
so for example Microsoft has their five
model yeah 54 was recently released it's
very good in my use it even is
hallucinating it told you they doesn't
know the answer yeah so these small
models that typically don't have the
World Knowledge for a lot of
applications you don't need those yeah
so it's better to save cost and and to
get faster responses to go with smaller
models larger models maybe you do need
more creativity yeah and there are
different different models tell stories
in different ways for something more
creative so it's almost depending on
it's almost like the usage patterns of
how you would use that model what is
most important in the ux of a developer
using that model which is one of the
nice reasons we're seeing more and more
tools almost offering which model do you
want to use for this tool which kind of
makes it that much nicer on that point
yeah that's another thing I don't think
we're going to have one model that's
going to rule them all yeah I think
we're going to have different models for
different use cases that specialize on
different data sets and that's really
why you want to be experimenting with
different models depending on your use
cas going be using wildely different
models there's so many coming out now
play around experiment yeah try them out
amazing so we talked about a ton of
different tools let's talk about the
tools that don't exist this is the
harder bit right if if there is a tool
or if there is a problem that you have
today when where you think you know what
I'd really love for an AI tool to exist
that will take this pain away what would
that be what's the pain what's the tool
I think I'd like to see better
benchmarks so often times we're seeing
models perform better than another model
on a bench Mark and then that's not
translating really well to the real
world use cases once developers get
their hands on it and people start
experimenting with the outputs and for
their use cases so recently we saw 01
come out in December in the 12 days of
shitness and part part of the reason why
there was so much fanfare about it was
because it was scoring really high yeah
or at least the the pr mode with extra
test time compute so it was given more
time to answer questions it was doing
really well on R kgi's
Benchmark and rcgi came and said so for
the for the longest time this has been
seen as it once you start going really
well in this we really cl to AGI and the
creators on The Benchmark came out and
said no this wasn't a suitable test it
never was now we have to create
something else yeah so I feel like
thinking a little bit further ahead and
creating tests that are going to stand
the test of time and benchmarks are
always hard right because every time
someone puts a benchmark out that
benchmark's there to be played and I
think models going to be no different in
that respect and and it leads on from
what you just said as well about
developers choosing the best model for
them if they have some level of
realistic expectations to what they can
expect based on their needs that will
give them a short list at least of
models that they can try yeah no I think
that's a nice a nice re a request rather
that that would benefit us as an
industry for sure what about tools that
you existing tools then today that you
really want to play with but just
haven't had time what would be on your
list of if you had a week to play with
the various tools what would you pick
something that I'd really like to play
around with is anthropics mCP model
context protocol that they released end
of last year so it
allows different data sources to be
connected and allows you to use your AI
tools with them so for example you
create these things called servers comes
with a few so you have clients CLA the
CLA desktop app is an example of the
client it's not the only one you can
actually create your own but he has
access to these tools for example a
GitHub server you can essentially chat
with Claude in the Claude desktop app
and can it can do stuff in your GitHub
repositories you can create them for you
and modify them but there are lots of
examples of tools you can add to it so
for my development workflow it' be quite
useful to for example to connect it to
jira or my my ticket monitoring platform
and I typically write what I need to do
in lists I could get it in one goal
to make my list suitable for a for my
team to look at Yeah clean it up and
then send it to J and it could have
another tool that allows it to act on
those tickets yeah yeah so really a
gentic behavior yeah is something that
you could enable that's definitely
something I want to play around with
pair AI it's another V code Fork IDE but
I think what they're doing a little bit
different is they're not building the
piece themselves I think they're trying
to be a modular alternative to some the
other on like cursor they allow you to
bring other tools so example your code
completion the type thing everyone's
been talking about your code completion
they allow you to bring that in
something else for your chat something
else for essentially every piece that
where AI is included in the IDE they
allow you to use different Services
interesting so you can use the best of
each Best in Class software for each and
maybe build your own solution so that's
something I I I've heard about read
about a bit I definitely want to play
around a bit more you mentioned deep
seek as well is that something that
you've had much chance to play with just
yet or or is that a a future as well so
I've played around with it in the chat
interface on the website not the API so
much yeah deep seek came out about a
week ago and at the time of recording so
I think the reason deep seek has gone so
viral partly is because they're offering
the API for free so deep seek on the app
store has hit number one on both the US
and European app stores but it's a model
trained for under 6 million
deep SE R1 model was trained for under 6
million and it seems like from the The
Benchmark tests and from some user
testing yeah that it is on par with open
AI 01 reasoning model which is trained
for people suggest people are thinking
in the hundreds of millions so much
cheaper it came out of China and I think
it's I think everyone's really heard
about this I think part of it was
because it caused quite a rockus in the
stock market so Nvidia went down 16%
yeah I actually saw meta rise mhm um I
think partly because they are also doing
open source models with their their
llama series and to be honest I wasn't
too surprised by this so what we've been
seeing over the last last two years is
that open source has not been too far
behind proprietary so there was like
that famous quote we have no mo from a
leaked Google memo about how the models
themselves are not not enough to give
you a competitive Advantage especially
when big Tech has been spend chucking so
much money into this yeah yeah it's
quite interesting yeah but uh open
source has been around we started off
six months behind so go to three months
and then open old one was released last
month R1 released this month month
behind we've been seeing the Gap close
over time so I'm not too surprised yeah
and again with the cost we've seen
models train the first model to train at
a certain level state of the art costing
tons of money and then pretty soon after
we're seeing lots of smaller AI research
Labs come out with models that are
equivalent but trained at much smaller
costs yeah this has been happening for
quite a while already and I think people
are sort drawing the wrong conclusions
people are saying that oh look the
American Research Labs have been
spending so much money and they are
completely screwed and obviously maybe
but I think that's the wrong conclusion
to take from this so deep seeks research
was open sourced so the written papers
about it how they went about creating it
this knowledge is going to be taken by
all the American Research Labs big
and they're going to recreate it improve
their own models make them a lot cheaper
and they also have a hardware Advantage
because of the embargos of the latest
chips not being allowed to be sold to
China so there's still a massive
Hardware Advantage um that the US has
and the big tech companies have and what
they're going to do is take this
research make their models better and
there's something called Javon javon's
Paradox have you heard of it no so it's
when something gets more efficient you'd
expect us to be using less of it yeah so
in terms of compute when it's getting
cheaper in terms of Compu you'd expect
us to use less because the price is
coming down so much he opens up so much
more utility that usage goes up like
crazy yeah and now we have even higher
demand for compute yeah so nvidia's
stock price going down I think no makes
no no sense people saying that big Tech
is in a bad position I would say no
because they're not going to stop here
so they if we we just going to stop at
this level of models maybe people would
have have a case but the whole point of
these research Labs is to be pushing the
limits and building the best models that
they can and for that you require
compute yeah so I think yeah deep seek
is great but and it's amazing that this
is happening all happening in January
it's pushing more competition between
all the different labs and different
companies creating these models and I
think we're just going to see I think
this is just great for us means that
we're getting better models uh open a
made the decision to the when the O free
mini model is going to released soon and
they said that's going to be free for
everybody yeah and I believe that's in
part due to the pressure from DC yeah
I'd feel stressed if I were for a model
company wouldn't you just constantly
just feeling like oh my gosh it's it's
constant jumping who's jumping ahead at
which time and you having to always
catch up or try and keep that lead right
this must be pretty stressful to keep
pushing let's talk about one of the
other things actually just in terms of
hackathon projects because I know
hackathons have been wildly popular
again now with just seeing whether it's
a internal company hackathon where
people are just trying to work out how
they can use AI to improve their
processes or automations and things like
that any good hackathon style projects
that you've seen uh recently so I did
see a project recently where these two
guys they built using Gemini 2.0 flash
which is a multimodel model so you can
access it can view understand images
video and speech so what they as well as
text and give responses as well in audio
or text form what they did was they
built an app you'd use to film your
house MH so it would analyze everything
inside your house using another object
detention model I think that they used
and it makes a catalog of all your
belongings valuable possessions in your
house and the use case for this was
actually insurance so okay if usually
you'd have to estimate the value of uh
your property and possessions mhm if you
undervalue this if something God forbid
was to go wrong then you're not going to
get full compensation if you overbid
then the premiums are paying are too
high yeah they built this in two days 10
minutes you walk around your house it
cataloges all your items gives your
valuation and now this can be used by
insurance companies obviously with more
development like I said production takes
a while yeah but it could be used by
insurance companies
to value your properties yeah yeah as
much as that sounds useful it also
sounds like a security nightmare but but
but in a couple of days it's amazing
what you can do with that kind of thing
so that's brilliant final question you
obviously read a ton watching YouTube
watching clips of of of the new
developments of various AI tools and
methodologies where' you go though to
maybe pick two or three sites what are
the what are the what are the sources of
news and and and good in-depth uh
content for you I use a huge variety of
sources probably what I use the most is
YouTube yep so my few channels I'd
recommend are for developers Indie Dev
Dan and all about AI yeah I feel like
they really do their due diligence when
it comes to using the latest tools
models and having good insight and
there's also AI explain because I feel
like he talks more about the B
implications of the developments that
happening so to stay more up toate with
the news I feel like that's another good
Channel I also use Discord so following
different project discords there's
usually a lot going on there people are
building all types of interesting
projects yeah yeah Twitter and Reddit
are really good for getting people's
perspective like the latest news when
someone hears about something that we
post about on Twitter when people have
been experimenting about stuff they'll
have discussions about it on Reddit I
feel like these are very good platforms
to be using and and a lot of the top
researchers and companies are all on
Twitter as well yeah constantly posting
about stuff so it's really and
researches so it's really it's that
first source of information where where
it's first yeah where it hits yeah yeah
comes to the first product Hunt is a
really good resource as well so these
are projects that are people have really
thought about so not just demos people
are really thinking how am I going to
get this production and tons of really
inative stuff there and plus it ranks
itself right so people vote and rank we
you see the best of what's coming out
yeah yeah oh that's cool lots of great
tips there as to where people can go
amazing far it's been an absolute
pleasure chatting with you and and yeah
great to have the Practical tips and the
users perspective as to what they're
using so thank you very much for sharing
no worries and for those of you who are
interested in our Discord and youtube'
of course got the AI native Dev on
YouTube as well as Discord where we can
talk about a ton of news to tips tricks
and various new tools and things that
people are trying in our in our AI
ecosystem as well make sure you
subscribe if you like the content
enjoying the content and thanks very
much for listening tune in to the next
episode thank you see
[Music]
you thanks for tuning in join us next
time on the AI native Dev brought to you
by Tesla